<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Kahaniya</string>


    <string name="warning">Currently showing 5 category,If you like to see 5 more Category please see 1 min video </string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "3D world.\n\n"

        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

        "Light and shadow.\n\n"

        "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create "
        "directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n"
        "Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android "
        "development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at "
        "various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the "
        "y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n"

        "Resting elevation.\n\n"

        "All material objects, regardless of size, have a resting elevation, or default elevation "
        "that does not change. If an object changes elevation, it should return to its resting "
        "elevation as soon as possible.\n\n"

        "Component elevations.\n\n"

        "The resting elevation for a component type is consistent across apps (e.g., FAB elevation "
        "does not vary from 6dp in one app to 16dp in another app).\n"
        "Components may have different resting elevations across platforms, depending on the depth "
        "of the environment (e.g., TV has a greater depth than mobile or desktop).\n\n"

        "Responsive elevation and dynamic elevation offsets.\n\n"

        "Some component types have responsive elevation, meaning they change elevation in response "
        "to user input (e.g., normal, focused, and pressed) or system events. These elevation "
        "changes are consistently implemented using dynamic elevation offsets.\n"
        "Dynamic elevation offsets are the goal elevation that a component moves towards, relative "
        "to the component’s resting state. They ensure that elevation changes are consistent "
        "across actions and component types. For example, all components that lift on press have "
        "the same elevation change relative to their resting elevation.\n"
        "Once the input event is completed or cancelled, the component will return to its resting "
        "elevation.\n\n"

        "Avoiding elevation interference.\n\n"

        "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between "
        "their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass "
        "through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways, "
        "whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n"
        "On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference. "
        "For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a "
        "user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n"
        "On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference. "
        "For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere "
        "when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_viewhome">Home</string>
    <string name="title_activity_viewsub_cat">Detail View</string>


    <string-array name="storyArray1">
        <item>Here are numerous simple short stories. These short stories are for all people to read. We all enjoy reading short stories. After the introduction of computer and the invention of internet, many people come to internet to spend their leisure time. Reading short stories online is the best pastime for many people around the world. Those who spend time with computers and internet have become accustomed to reading the stories online. This habit has started to keep the people within the four walls of the office room. The children have become accustomed to listening to stories told by the narrators. The schools also have started to use the internet. Many schools have started to maintain their own knowledge base with many such short stories. Such is the power of the internet. The future will never be bright without computer and internet. </item>
        <item>This Short Story Three Simple Rules is quite interesting to all the people. Enjoy reading this story.

Once there was a rich man in Thailand. His name was Chulong. He was a very rich man. Yet he wanted more riches, more money.

One day he was walking in his garden. He saw a strange bird in a bush. It was very small. But it had very beautiful and colorful features. Its voice was also very sweet. Chulong had never seen such a bird in his life. He slowly went near the bush unseen. He caught the bird. Now the bird began to speak.

“Why have you caught me?" the bird asked.

“I want to make money. I can sell you for a big amount," replied Chulong.

“But you are already rich. Why do you want more?" asked the bird.

“Because I want to become richer and richer," replied Chulong.

“But do not dream of making money through me!" said the bird. It further added, “You can not sell me. Nobody will buy me, because, in imprisonment, I lose my beauty and my sweet voice." Then it slowly turned into a black bird.

The beautiful features were now looking like the feathers of a crow.

Chulong hopes of making money were shattered. He said angrily, “I will kill you, and I will eat your meat."

“Eat me! I am so small. You will not get any meat out of me," replied the bird.

Chulong could not answer. The bird then suggested, “Well set me free. In return I shall teach you three simple but useful rules."

“What is the use of the rules? I want only money," said Chulong. He was irritated.

“But these rules can profit you greatly," added the bird.

“Profit me! Really? Then I shall set you free. But how can I trust you? You may fly away," said Chulong.

“I give you my word. And I always keep my word," said the bird.

Chulong wanted to take a chance. He released the bird. It flew up at once. Then it sat on the branch of a tree. Its color started changing. It became beautiful again.

Chulong asked, “Now teach me the rules."

“Certainly," said the bird.

Then it added, “The first rule is Never Believe everything others say. The second rule is Never be sad about something you do not have. The third rule is Never throw away what you have in your hand."

“You silly bird," shouted Chulong. And he added, “These three rules are known to every one. You have cheated me."

But the bird said, “Chulong, just sit down for a while. Think about all your actions of today. You had me in your hands, but you threw me away (released me). You believed all that I said. And you are sad about not having me. The rules are simple. But you never followed them. Now do you see the value of the rules?" so saying the bird flew away and disappeared from his sight.</item>
        <item>Story3</item>
        <item>Story4</item>
        <item>Story5</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="storyArray11">
        <item>Here are numerous simple short stories. These short stories are for all people to read. We all enjoy reading short stories. After the introduction of computer and the invention of internet, many people come to internet to spend their leisure time. Reading short stories online is the best pastime for many people around the world. Those who spend time with computers and internet have become accustomed to reading the stories online. This habit has started to keep the people within the four walls of the office room. The children have become accustomed to listening to stories told by the narrators. The schools also have started to use the internet. Many schools have started to maintain their own knowledge base with many such short stories. Such is the power of the internet. The future will never be bright without computer and internet. </item>
        <item>This Short Story Three Simple Rules is quite interesting to all the people. Enjoy reading this story.

Once there was a rich man in Thailand. His name was Chulong. He was a very rich man. Yet he wanted more riches, more money.

One day he was walking in his garden. He saw a strange bird in a bush. It was very small. But it had very beautiful and colorful features. Its voice was also very sweet. Chulong had never seen such a bird in his life. He slowly went near the bush unseen. He caught the bird. Now the bird began to speak.

“Why have you caught me?" the bird asked.

“I want to make money. I can sell you for a big amount," replied Chulong.

“But you are already rich. Why do you want more?" asked the bird.

“Because I want to become richer and richer," replied Chulong.

“But do not dream of making money through me!" said the bird. It further added, “You can not sell me. Nobody will buy me, because, in imprisonment, I lose my beauty and my sweet voice." Then it slowly turned into a black bird.

The beautiful features were now looking like the feathers of a crow.

Chulong hopes of making money were shattered. He said angrily, “I will kill you, and I will eat your meat."

“Eat me! I am so small. You will not get any meat out of me," replied the bird.

Chulong could not answer. The bird then suggested, “Well set me free. In return I shall teach you three simple but useful rules."

“What is the use of the rules? I want only money," said Chulong. He was irritated.

“But these rules can profit you greatly," added the bird.

“Profit me! Really? Then I shall set you free. But how can I trust you? You may fly away," said Chulong.

“I give you my word. And I always keep my word," said the bird.

Chulong wanted to take a chance. He released the bird. It flew up at once. Then it sat on the branch of a tree. Its color started changing. It became beautiful again.

Chulong asked, “Now teach me the rules."

“Certainly," said the bird.

Then it added, “The first rule is Never Believe everything others say. The second rule is Never be sad about something you do not have. The third rule is Never throw away what you have in your hand."

“You silly bird," shouted Chulong. And he added, “These three rules are known to every one. You have cheated me."

But the bird said, “Chulong, just sit down for a while. Think about all your actions of today. You had me in your hands, but you threw me away (released me). You believed all that I said. And you are sad about not having me. The rules are simple. But you never followed them. Now do you see the value of the rules?" so saying the bird flew away and disappeared from his sight.</item>
        <item>Story3</item>
        <item>Story4</item>
        <item>Story5</item>
        <item>Story6</item>
        <item>Story7</item>
        <item>Story8</item>
        <item>Story9</item>
        <item>Story10</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="storyArray2">
        <item>Story1</item>
        <item>Story2</item>
        <item>Story3</item>
        <item>Story4</item>
        <item>Story5</item>
        <item>Story6</item>
        <item>Story7</item>
        <item>Story8</item>
        <item>Story9</item>
        <item>Story10</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="storyArray3">
        <item>Story1</item>
        <item>Story2</item>
        <item>Story3</item>
        <item>Story4</item>
        <item>Story5</item>
        <item>Story6</item>
        <item>Story7</item>
        <item>Story8</item>
        <item>Story9</item>
        <item>Story10</item>
        <item>Story11</item>
        <item>Story12</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="storyArray4">
        <item>Story1</item>
        <item>Story2</item>
        <item>Story3</item>
        <item>Story4</item>
        <item>Story5</item>
        <item>Story6</item>
        <item>Story7</item>
        <item>Story8</item>
        <item>Story9</item>
        <item>Story10</item>
        <item>Story11</item>
        <item>Story12</item>
        <item>Story13</item>
        <item>Story14</item>
        <item>Story15</item>
        <item>Story16</item>
        <item>Story17</item>
        <item>Story18</item>
        <item>Story19</item>
        <item>Story20</item>
        <item>Story21</item>

    </string-array>


    <string-array name="storyArray5">
        <item>Story1</item>
        <item>Story2</item>
        <item>Story3</item>
        <item>Story4</item>
        <item>Story5</item>
        <item>Story6</item>
        <item>Story7</item>
        <item>Story8</item>
        <item>Story9</item>
        <item>Story10</item>
        <item>Story11</item>
        <item>Story12</item>
        <item>Story13</item>
        <item>Story14</item>
        <item>Story15</item>
        <item>Story16</item>
        <item>Story17</item>
        <item>Story18</item>
        <item>Story19</item>
        <item>Story20</item>
        <item>Story21</item>
        <item>Story22</item>
        <item>Story22</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="storyArray6">
        <item>Story1</item>
        <item>Story2</item>
        <item>Story3</item>
        <item>Story4</item>
        <item>Story5</item>
        <item>Story6</item>
        <item>Story7</item>
        <item>Story8</item>
        <item>Story9</item>
        <item>Story10</item>
        <item>Story11</item>
        <item>Story12</item>
        <item>Story13</item>
        <item>Story14</item>
        <item>Story15</item>
        <item>Story16</item>
        <item>Story17</item>
        <item>Story18</item>
        <item>Story19</item>
        <item>Story20</item>
        <item>Story21</item>
        <item>Story22</item>
        <item>Story22</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="storyArray7">
        <item>Story1</item>
        <item>Story2</item>
        <item>Story3</item>
        <item>Story4</item>
        <item>Story5</item>
        <item>Story6</item>
        <item>Story7</item>
        <item>Story8</item>
        <item>Story9</item>
        <item>Story10</item>
        <item>Story11</item>
        <item>Story12</item>
        <item>Story13</item>
        <item>Story14</item>
        <item>Story15</item>
        <item>Story16</item>
        <item>Story17</item>
        <item>Story18</item>
        <item>Story19</item>
        <item>Story20</item>
        <item>Story21</item>
        <item>Story22</item>
        <item>Story22</item>
        <item>Story23</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="storyArray8">
        <item>Story1</item>
        <item>Story2</item>
        <item>Story3</item>
        <item>Story4</item>
        <item>Story5</item>
        <item>Story6</item>
        <item>Story7</item>
        <item>Story8</item>
        <item>Story9</item>
        <item>Story10</item>
        <item>Story11</item>
        <item>Story12</item>
        <item>Story13</item>
        <item>Story14</item>
        <item>Story15</item>
        <item>Story16</item>
        <item>Story17</item>
        <item>Story18</item>
        <item>Story19</item>
        <item>Story20</item>
        <item>Story21</item>
        <item>Story22</item>
        <item>Story22</item>
        <item>Story23</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="storyArray9">
        <item>Story1</item>
        <item>Story2</item>
        <item>Story3</item>
        <item>Story4</item>
        <item>Story5</item>
        <item>Story6</item>
        <item>Story7</item>
        <item>Story8</item>
        <item>Story9</item>
        <item>Story10</item>
        <item>Story11</item>
        <item>Story12</item>
        <item>Story13</item>
        <item>Story14</item>
        <item>Story15</item>
        <item>Story16</item>
        <item>Story17</item>
        <item>Story18</item>
        <item>Story19</item>
        <item>Story20</item>
        <item>Story21</item>
        <item>Story22</item>
        <item>Story22</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="storyArray10">
        <item>Story1</item>
        <item>Story2</item>
        <item>Story3</item>
        <item>Story4</item>
        <item>Story5</item>
        <item>Story6</item>
        <item>Story7</item>
        <item>Story8</item>
        <item>Story9</item>
        <item>Story10</item>
        <item>Story11</item>
        <item>Story12</item>
        <item>Story13</item>
        <item>Story14</item>
        <item>Story15</item>
        <item>Story16</item>
        <item>Story17</item>
        <item>Story18</item>
        <item>Story19</item>
        <item>Story20</item>
        <item>Story21</item>
        <item>Story22</item>
        <item>Story22</item>
    </string-array>


</resources>
